I want to be in the loop before you email my mother in law.
And what are you here to learn at AI?
I'm here to learn about observability and deterministic models,
just to see how to make the results of AI more trusting.
And even with a proper enterprise scale adoption of AI,
how do you make sure that the models are not like still hallucinating?
Or if they are like the eval metrics are catching that
and we're able to determine what's actually going on under the hood.
Yeah.
So we're now in a place where there's so much value, so much data
going through our AI, our harnesses that we're going to need to figure out
how do we control these things?
Yeah, I think that's probably next is yes, I've got 20 loops going but okay,
what next?
I always ask this question would you trust an agent
to send an email on your behalf right now, sight unseen?
What I do, actually, this is a very valid question
because I've just literally just built a nice little app called Simon EA
and it can read all my emails and things like that.
But what I get it to do is I get it to only write emails and leave them in draft.
It doesn't have the send ability, so I validate every single thing
that goes out my outbox.
So this like incredibly powerful tool and you have to review every email before
it gets sent because that moment where it shifts to impacting, you know,
somebody’s opinion of you outside of your own organization,
like that's an important line that it's going to cross.
A non reversible as well.
It's non-reversible.
It's not a retaining door.
Yeah.
If the agent had spent the day reading your diary,
if the person it was going to send a message to was like your mother in law.
Yeah. All right. You want to be able to express those circumstances.
If you spent the day reading my diary, then I want to be in the loop before
you email my mother in law.